# José Miguel Quesada **Campos**

Frontend Developer

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a Frontend developer with 2 years of experience, working for projects that will be use for people all around the country, using technologies such Javascript, typescript, Redux, Ionic. I excel at problem solving and adding value to the companies I work for. I am interested in keep applying my knowledge and skills to contribute to the grow of the industry.

### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- React
- Redux
- Ionic
- Next.js
- Gatsby
- Angular
- Boostrap
- SCSS
- Git

# CONTACT



+58 4122120037





Caracas, Venezuela

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Fibex Telecom | November, 2021 – July, 2022

- I collaborated in the development of 5 applications that are right now in production and are being used by users nationwide, developed for web, tablet, mobile, and TV devices.
- I was in charge of developing responsive user interfaces, APIs, and database management, following the principles of clean code (DRY, SOLID, OOP).
- I led the development of one fullstack project in which I was the only one in charge, developing the frontend with React, the backend with Node.js, the database with SQL, and using MYSQL database management.
- I developed microservices in Node.js and PHP to integrate into several applications.
- I successfully worked with technologies I never used before, by learning by myself using the official docs of every technology.
- I used different technologies such as JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Ionic, Angular, SCSS, Nodejs, PHP, SQL, and Roku.

# Prolesys Consultores C.A. | July, 2022 - August, 2023

- I collaborated in the development of 4 applications that are right now in production and are being used by users nationwide; where I was in charge of developing responsive user interfaces, following the principles of clean code (DRY, SOLID).
- I led the development of two frontend projects in which I was the only one in charge.
- I collaborated in the planning and structuring of the projects I work for, intending to make scalable and stable applications.
- I developed reusable and scalable code that contributed to decreasing the amount of code making the apps more performance.
- I integrated the APIs developed by the backend team, to make complete and functional apps.
- I solved important bugs in production in the estimated time.
- I used different technologies such as JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Ionic, Gatsby, Bootstrap, and Electron.
- I helped mentor the junior developers in working with React, and Ionic.

## **LANGUAGES**

English: Proficiency C2

Spanish: Native

# **EDUCATION**

2017 - Present | Caracas - Venezuela

#### **Economics**

Universidad Central de Venezuela